如果又有什么事情发生了
Something broke here.
我没说都会没事
I'm not saying it's not.
我们对事情的看法不再一样了
We don't see things the same way anymore.
我们看待事物的角度也不一样了
Our roles in this whole thing.
我没办法再相信你了
I can't trust you.
可我们是一家人
We are family.
你说得好像这句话就是万灵药一样
You say that like it's some sort of cure-all.
好像这样就能改变事实
Like it can change the fact.
我们之间所有的事情
That everything.
之所以会如此
That have ever gone wrong between us.
都是因为我们是一家人
Has been because we're family.
十五
Fifteen.
十四
Fourteen.
十三
Thirteen.
十二
Twelve.
十一
Eleven.
十
Ten.
九
Nine.
八
Eight.
七
Seven.
- 六 - 不能那么小口
- Six - No chipmunking allowed.
五
Five.
- 四三二 - 咽下去 不然你就失去资格了
- Four, three, two - Swallow!Or you're disqualified.
一
One.
看来我们分出胜负了
Looks like we got a winner.
他作弊了
He cheated.
你个瘦猴 滚开 我可是赢得正大光明
Hey, back off, Skeletor.I won fair and square.
说得真像这么回事
Like hell you did, Jabba.
我看见你把一个热狗塞进裤子了
I saw you slip a hotdog in your pocket.
兄弟 我不想这么说
I hate to break it to you, pal.
但是我裤子里的可不是热狗
But that's not hot dog.
噢噢
Oh.
嘿
Hey.
你昨晚睡觉了吗
You go to bed last night.
什么
What.
没有
Eh…no.
在放Rudy
No, "Rudy" was on.
放不可原谅的时候 我已经睡不着了
"Unforgiven", and then I was too jacked to sleep.
所以 还是起来做研究了
So, research.
因为Gadreel
Gadreel.
Metatron 该隐之印 还有
Yeah, Metatron, Mark of Cain and.
该死的蟋蟀
Crickets.
不过找到了个案子
I did find a case, though.
是吗
Oh yeah.
没错
Yeah.
是场离奇的死亡
Was a strange death in.
在明尼苏达 斯蒂尔沃特
Stillwater Minnesota.
一名参赛选手在吃热狗比赛之后死亡了
A competitive eater died after a hot dog eating contest.
怎么 因为热狗吗
So, what?Death by tube steak.
只可能是这样
If only.
他在自己车里遭到袭击
He got attack in his car.
不过 听听这个
But, get this.
他的体重从三百磅缩减到了九十磅
He shrunk from three hundred pounds to ninety pounds.
女巫的巫术
Witchcraft.
还是因为强力泻药
Or a heavy-duty laxative.
来吗
You game.
当然
Yeah.
很好
Good.
我去冲个澡
Looks like it's a whore's bath for me.
五分钟就好
I will be ready in five.
你确定你没事吗 Dean
You sure you're okay, Dean.
我为什么会有事
Why wouldn't I be.
我不知道
I don't know, you.
不是因为我那天说的话 是吧
This isn't about what I said the other day, is it.
关于我们不应该再做兄弟的话
About we are not suppose to be brothers.
别自作多情了
No, don't flatter yourself.
我没那么脆弱
I don't break that easy.
很好 因为我只是说了实话
Good, cause I was just being honest.
是啊 我听得清清楚楚
Oh yeah.I got that loud and clear.
多谢你们的耐心等等 探员们
Thanks for your paitients, agents.
Coroner的报告终于来了
Coroner's report finally came in.
好的 谢谢
All right, thank you.
看看
Let's see.
受害者在死亡之前
Did Wayne McNut really weight three hundred pounds.
真的重达三百磅吗
Just moments before the time of death.
准确的说是三百十六磅
Three hundred sixteen to be exact.
官方的死亡原因是
And the official cause of death.
心搏停止
Cardiac arrest.
不过也只在你我之间说说
But between you and me.
这还只是个猜测
That's just a guess.
受害者有大量器官遭到损坏
The vic suffered massive organ damage.
给你 Jenny
Here you go, Jenny.
脾破裂
Ruptured spleen.
肝脏穿孔
Pierced liver.
肺部被拍碎
Collapsed lung.
就好像所有东西从他身体里被吸出来了
Looks like everthing just sucked right out of him.
就好像他被吸尘器给吸干了
Like he'd been hoovered.
是啊
Yeah, you know.
我必须诚实的说 伙计们
I gotta be honest, fellas.
我们简直惊呆了
We are stumped.
这种事情不会发生在斯蒂尔沃特
This type of thing just doesn't happened in Stillwater.
他平时有仇人吗
Did Wayne have any enemies.
只是不大友好的竞争对手
More like an unfriendly rivalry.
一个叫瘦子Jim Morgan的人
A guy named "Slim Jim" Morgan.
像Wayne一样 他因为参加
Like Wayne, he was pretty well-known.
大胃王比赛而出名
In the competitive eating circuit.
在这里那算是件大事吗
Is that a big thing out here.
是的 没错
Oh, yeah, you betcha.
市民把这些比赛看得很重要
Folks take it real seriously.
会花上几个月去训练 吃些乱七八糟的东西
Train for months, eat all sorts of wackadoo stuff.
比如烤豆 鸡翅 黄油
You know, like, bake beans, buff wings, butter.
黄油
Butter.
没错 有时候还是油炸的
Yeah, sometimes deep fried.
光是今年
This year alone.
Wayne赢得了黄油超级碗
Wayne won the Butter Bow.
鸡翅比赛 还有吃鲜虾大赛
The Wing Ding and Shrimptasia.
但是重点是
Anywoo, point being.
Wayne McNut是整个地区唯一一个
Wayne McNut was the only one.
瘦子Jim打败不了的人
Slim Jim couldn't beat in the whole region.
所以他就是嫌疑犯了
So is he the suspect.
我们去调查过他
We checked him out.
但是Wince死亡的时候
But Slim Jim was in the Hot Doggery.
Slim Jim正在热狗大赛里
The time of Wayne's death.
有15个目击证人可以证明
We got fifteen witnesses to prove it.
真的吗
Really.
是的
Yeah.
只是在训练
Training.
每次我准备比赛前 我都会吃生菜
When I gear up a competition, I eat lettuce.
这能锻炼我的肠胃
It strenches the stomach.
有理由远离沙拉了
It's a reason to stay away from salad.
你了解Wayne McNut多少
How well did you know Wayne McNut.
我只知道他是个卑鄙的作弊者
What I have to know is he is a weasel and a cheat.
我不想这么说 不过这就是因果报应
I hate to say it, but karma's a bitch.
这东西有点意思
This is interesting.
Mala的幸运符
Mala's good-luck charms.
那么Mala是谁
And Mala is.
我的妻子
My old lady.
你妻子很迷信吗
Is your lady superstitious.
是的 她是Romanichal
Yeah, she is Romanichal.
Romanichal
Romanichal.
就是吉普赛人
Gypsy.
我不这样称呼她
But don't call her that.
她说这很掉价
She says it's reductive.
但是我觉得这是种赞美
But I think it's a compliment.
我是说电视节目上的吉普赛人很多啊
I mean Gypsies are all the range on TV.
比如 我的盛大吉普赛婚礼 吉普赛姐妹
My big fat Gypsy wedding, Gypsy sisters.
跟上卡戴珊的时尚脚步
Keeping up with Kardashians.
你介意我用一下你的卫生间吗
You mind if I use your bathroom.
不介意 去吧
Yeah, go ahead.
但是用楼上后面那个
But use the one up the stairs at the back.
我妻子在主卫里面洗澡
Mala's taking a shower in ours.
你真的以一个热狗之差输掉了比赛吗
Did you really lose the "Wiener Winner" by one dog.
是的
Yeah.
我们说到哪了 六英尺长
And what are we talking?Six inches?Foot-long.
探员先生 我现在难道是嫌疑人吗
Agent, am I a suspect here or what.
除非你们手里有搜查证
Cause…unless you got a warrant.
- 可以了吗 - 没问题了
- Ready to go? - Yea.
Morgan先生 我们感谢您的配合
Mr.Morgan, we thank you for your time.
如果你想起什么其他情况
If you remember anything else.
这是我们的电话
This is our number.
我们会待在这里
And where we're staying locally.
我们这里有了Wayne McNut的头发
So we got what appear to be Wayne McNut's hair.
和一袋子诡异的东西
And a bag full of weird.
在Romanichal文化里
And in the Romanichal culture.
这个袋子被称作浦西巫术袋
The pouch is called Putsi Bag.
是用来下诅咒的
It's used for hexes.
所以Mala在丈夫的比赛上下了诅咒吗
So what?Mala's putting hexes on hubby's competition.
我们要对付的是什么
I mean, what do we got ourselves.
瘦针什么的吗
A "thinner" sitch here.
瘦子Jim可能都不知道
Slim Jim might not even know.
你好
Hi.
我知道你们拿了我的东西
I believe you have something of mine.
杀了Wayne么可能 我爱他
Kill Wayne?I loved him.
所以 你们
So, you were.
是的我们一直在偷情
Yes, okay, we are having an affair.
事实上 好几年了
For years, actually.
我不想失礼
I don't mean to be rude.
但是 你怎么会喜欢他那种类型
But…how is it Wayne McNut is your type.
我是说 你结婚的那个男人如此瘦弱年轻
I mean, you're married to a man who is barely a buck, wet.
怎么说呢 有时候赠与的感觉很好
What can I say, sometimes it's nice to feel a little give.
噢我明白啦
Oh, I get that.
就像加一点调料
A little cushion for the.
帮我解释一下
Help me understand something.
如果你爱他 为什么你还要诅咒他
If you love Wayne, why did you put a curse on him.
那不是诅咒
It wasn't a curse.
浦西巫术袋也可以用来保佑别人的
Putsi Bags are also used for blessings.
我希望他能赢
I wanted Wayne to win.
原来计划是拿到财产就赶紧离婚
Plan was, take the prize money, get the quickie divorce.
然后在奥兰多结婚
And then tie the knot in Orlando.
Wayne以前叫我茉莉公主
Wayne used to call me princess Jasmine.
我居然又胖了
I gained weight.
这怎么可能
How is that even possible.
谁在那儿
Hello.
有人吗
Anyone there.
重称一次
Let's try this again.
受害人之前多重
Any idea what the vic weighed beforehand.
165磅
165.
其实是 180磅
So, 180.
众所周知 所有女人都在体重和年龄上撒谎
Known fact.All women lie about their weight and age.
等等 我怎么记得你跟那个女服务生说你29岁
Wait, you told that waitress the other day you were 29.
还需要什么吗 探员
Need anything else?Agents.
Hanscum警长什么时候来
Yeah, is sheriff Hanscum around.
抱歉 这周她去休假了
Sorry, she's out for the rest of the week.
真是会挑时候啊是不是
Hell of a time to take a vacation right.
好吧
Okay.
眼下有两个
So we have two victims.
看起来毫无关联的受害人
With seemingly nothing in common except.
对甜食的极度热爱
The love for eclairs.
看这个
Check this out.
这是什么 胎记吗
What is that, a birthmark.
不知怎么体重减轻了是吧
So the weight had to come off somehow, right.
如果这是个吸痕呢
What if it's a suction mark.
吸痕
Suction mark.
换生灵
Okay, changeling.
但它们不对孩子下手
Yeah but changelings don't take over kids.
这两个受害者都没有孩子
Neither of the vics had any.
我没不知道Wayne McNut有没有吸痕
We don't know if Wayne McNut had a suction mark.
除非我们疏忽了
Unless we missed it.
嗯
Yeah.
我们应该分头行动
We should split up.
一个去停尸房看看
One of us should hit the morgue.
另一个留在这儿跟工作人员聊聊
The other should stat here and question the staff.
我留下吧
I'll stay.
不行
Ain't gonna happen.
怎么了
Why.
你和女的相处得奇怪
Because you are weird around girls.
什么叫奇怪
What does that mean, weird.
尴尬的那种奇怪 Sam那种奇怪
Awkward-weird.Sam-weired.
抱歉兄弟 我说实话而已
Sorry man.I'm just being honest.
昨晚是你值班关闭体育馆
So you were scheduled to close the gym last night.
对 但我并没关门
Yeah, but I didn't exactly lock up.
Carol还在健身而我马上有个约会
Carol was still working out and I had a date.
但我不想因此而耽误了她
And I didn't want to shortchange her you know.
她为了自己的婚礼不惜一切代价
I mean the poor girls had been working so hard.
想要减肥成功
To lose weight for her wedding.
所以我把钥匙交给她
I slipped her the key.
让她走时锁门就好
And I told her to lock up on her way out.
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
嗨
Hey.
在停尸房有什么发现吗
Got anything at the morgue.
Wayne虽然已经瘦得不成人形了
Yeah.So Wayne was banged pretty bad.
但是还能看出在他脖子后面 发际线以下的地方
But on the back of his neck just below his hairline.
有一个吸吮痕迹
Suction mark.
和Carol的一样
Identical to Carol's.
这么说他们都被标记了
Okay so they both have marks.
就像是在罗兹体育馆工作的那个性感教练
Just like the hot trainer at Rollz.
她很瘦而且她还活着
She was skinny and alive.
刚刚减下很多重量
And just recently lost a ton of weight.
我一问那个印是怎么回事
When I asked about the mark.
她就尴尬起来 不说话了
She clammed up, got all embarrassed.
所以我查了一下 最后发现
So I did some checking and it turns out that.
看样子她上个月去这个地方
She took a couple me days last month.
休息了几天
And went here.
大峡谷健身中心
Canyon Valley.
对
Yeah.
当你照镜子时
When you look in the mirror.
你认得镜子里同样在注视你的胖子吗
Do you recognize the fat person staring back at you.
你是否试过所有的减肥食谱和瘦身锻炼
Have you tried every fat diet every fitness trend out there.
但效果却差强人意
But it turned out nothing seemed to work.
在大峡谷健身中心
Here at Canyon Valley.
我们保证不用手术即可减肥
We guarantee weight loss with no surgery.
无须采用极端食谱
No extreme diet.
无须采用高强度训练法
And no intensive workout regimen.
一星期保证有效
Guaranteed results in one week.
你可以达到减肥目标
You can reach your weight loss goals.
我们就达到了
We did.
你还在犹豫什么 拿起你手中的电话
But only if you reach for the phone.
在大峡谷健身中心预定位置吧
And call Canyon Valley.Now.
那个地方离这多远
How far away is that place.
离这儿不远
A couple of hours.
我们看了网上的广告片很受触动
We were really really moved by the online testimonials.
非常给力
Oh yeah it was some powerful stuff.
你们两个都是专业的健身教练吗
And you boys are both certified personal trainers.
没错 我们是私人健身教练兄弟组合
Yeah.Personal training brothers.
有点像Hans和Franz 只不过不是德国人
Kinda like Hans and Franz but less German.
你的专长是
And you're certified in.
让人出汗
Making people sweat.
叱咤风云雷厉风行 这是我们的风格
Yeah.Kicking ass and taking names.It's how we do.
简单解释一下 我哥的意思是
To clarify.What my brother is trying to say is.
我们俩都热爱健身和帮助他人
We both have a passion for fitness and helping people.
我们也是 其实我们就是因此相遇的
Us too.In fact, that's how we first met.
我是Maritza在秘鲁的第一个客户
I was Maritza's first client back in Peru.
当时我在留学
I was on a student visa.
想家 压力大 企图以吃解闷
Homesick, stressed, eating my troubles away.
他胖得像房子一样大
Oh he was a size of a casa.
确实是这样
Oh it's true.
我当时差点儿就得了心脏病
I was one empanada away from a heart attack.
但是后来 我碰上了这位神赐般的人
But then this gorgeous godsend made me.
于是才有了今天这个壮实健康的我
The lean, mean, fighting machine I am today.
我扯远了 好消息是我们招人
But I digressed.The good news is we are hiring.
坏消息是
The bad news is.
我们只有一个健身教练的空位
There's only one training position available.
去别的部门工作怎么样
How do you feel about working in another department.
短裤不错
Nice shorts.
发网不错
Nice hairnet.
凭什么让我来当食堂阿姨
Yeah.Why do I get to be the lunch lady.
你从什么时候起挨着吃的还抱怨了
Since when do you ever complain about being around food.
这才不是吃的
Okay, this is not food.
嘿 新来的
Hey, new guy.
别和教练搭讪了 快回来干活
Quit flirting with the trainer and keep scoopin.
没事
It's alright.
我的瑜伽班还有五分钟就开始了
My, uh, Ashtanga yoga class starts in five minutes.
你是怎么学会瑜伽的
How the hell do you know anything about yoga.
跟瑜伽老师约过会的可不止你一个人
You're not the only one who’s ever dated someone bendy.
嘿 你这儿有燕麦粥吗
Hey, you have any oatmeal.
我倒想有
Yeah I wish.
但是我们有豆腐做的
No but we have something that's tofu over there.
这是什么玩意儿
What is that.
大概是煎饼 也是豆腐的
It's a pancake, it's tofu.
我知道听起来很胆小 但是我想问
I fell like a baby asking this but.
这种疗法疼吗
Will the treatment hurt.
一点也不
Not at all.
拔罐的唯一缺点
The only drawback of cupping is.
就是会留下一个吸痕
It leaves a suction mark.
可能有点淤青
It can bruise a little.
拔罐
Cupping.
对 古代中国秘籍 明星都做这个
Yes, ancient Chinese secret.All the celebrities do it.
可以排毒 促进新陈代谢 感觉很舒服
It draws out toxin, boosts metabolism.You will feel good.
谁知道呢
Who knew.
抱歉
Excuse me.
这里太舒适了
It's just so relaxing in here.
这是香料疗法 薰衣草效果很强烈
It's the aromatherapy, the lavender really packs a punch.
天啊真暖和
Oh geez that's warm.
懒惰鬼
Flojo.
有你那点儿休息的功夫 你早把卫生做完了
You got time to lean, you got time to clean.
我饿死了
I'm starving.
我们吃什么
What do we get to eat.
和顾客们一样
Same with the clients.
他们想让我们吃兔粮吗
Do they expect us to eat this rabbit food.
这不是兔粮是营养餐
It's not rabbit food it's superfood.
我才不吃呢
I'm not eating that.
在大峡谷健身中心 员工首先要以身作则
At Canyon Valley, we lead by examples.
这就是咱们要以身做的则吗
This is leading-by example.
这不是给我们的 蠢蛋
It's not for us stupido.
是给客人的
It's for the clients.
他们被允许把布丁加到减肥理疗日的食谱里
They're allowed to put pudding on their a spa day.
就像是最后的狂欢一样
Like a, last hurrah for the real work starts.
开始工作吧
Get to work.
Frank 我们需要买进更多的笋
Hey, Frank, we need to order more asparagus.
好的
Okay.
谁想得到呢
What do you know.
今天也是我的减肥理疗日
It's my spa day too.
好的各位 慢慢提高 就像是倒趴在地上
Okay, good job guys, go to, uh, downward dog.
保持这个姿势五分钟
Hold for five minutes.
五分钟
Five minutes.
以前才30秒
It used to be thirty seconds.
没错 30秒 我就是这个意思
Yeah, right, thirty seconds, that's what I meant.
好的 我下来检查一下
Okay, just come around.
看看你们的姿势正不正确
Make sure everybody's form is okay.
确保你们跟上了课程进度 然后你们
Make sure you keep your cores tight and you.
做得很好 非常好
Good job, great.
把你们的腰挺直
Just straight your back out.
今天很不错 做得很好
Well done today, good job.
做得好 各位 做得好
Good work, guys, good work.
再见
Namaste, okay.
做得好 再见
Good work, see you all soon.
做得很好
Good job.
课上的怎么样
How was class.
很好 非常好
It's…uh great, yeah.
Freli探员
Agent Freli.
你在这做什么
What are you doing here.
Freli探员
Agent Freli.
我不知道 她现在精神状态不大好可能认错了
I don't know, she must be pretty out of it.
抱歉
Excuse me, sorry.
这个电话必须接
Got to get this.
是我 祝你有美好的一天
Yeah, have a good day.
Sammy
Sammy.
Dean 你怎么了
Dean, what's wrong with you.
我需要帮忙
Need your help.
你在哪儿 Dean
Where are you, Dean.
地瓜
Sweet potatoes.
Dean
Dean.
Sammy
Sammy.
Dean 嘿 嘿
Dean, hey, hey.
醒醒
Wake up.
怎么那么久
What took you so long.
到底发生了什么
What the hell happened.
我被下药了
I was drugged.
下药 你在说什么
Drugged, what.
那个布丁
Pudding.
本来是给客人准备的
It was supposed to be for the clients.
但我无法抗拒它的味道
But I couldn't resist.
咸味焦糖布丁
Salted caramel.
没错 兄弟 全世界最好的味道
Yeah, man, best of both the worlds.
又甜又咸
Salty and sweet.
好吧 你在这儿待着
Right, you stay here.
不 我和你一起
No, I'll go with you.
你先吧 我等下会去找你的
Go ahead, man, I'll catch up.
布丁是你做的吗
Hey, did you make the pudding.
不一定
It depends.
为什么
On what.
看你喜不喜欢咯
Whether you like or not.
这里面加了什么
What's in it.
放轻松 Jack Lalanne
Relax, Jack Lalanne.
里面有淡奶油 脱脂奶 海盐
It's low cal, non fat milk, sea salt.
不不不 不是材料
No, no, not the ingredients.
是其他的东西
The something extra.
冷静点儿 伙计 保健品好吧
Chill, man, supplements, okay.
什么保健品
What kind of supplements.
这个
Here, hey.
促进新陈代谢
To boost metalbolism.
经由Larry和Maritza推荐
Per Larry and Maritza.
不是这些保健品的关系 是催眠药
It's not supplyments, the roofies.
你怎么知道是催眠药
What, how do you know the roofies' like.
怎么可能不知道
How do you not know.
你觉得我会想要醒来时
You think I wanna end up in the.
发现自己在酒店浴缸里 发现肾被割掉吗
Hotel bath tub with my kidney carved out.
在车臣之类的鬼地方
In Chechnya.
你上瑜伽课有没有发现什么
Did you find anything out in the yoga.
有 掠夺者的身体烙印
Yeah, yeah, invasion of the body snatchers.
课上的每个人身上
Every single person in the class.
都有着诡异的吮吸痕迹
Has one of those freaky ass suction marks.
这里到底发生什么了
What the hell is going on here.
我不是故意要放你们鸽子的
You know, I didn't mean to bail on you, fellas.
但是我等了六个月
But, I've been waiting for six months to.
才进来大峡谷健身中心
Get into the Canyon Valley.
这真是太值了
I'm gonna tell you, it's worth it.
已经减了十磅了
Already lost ten pounds.
一天之内吗
In, in one day.
不要见怪
No offence.
警长 你看起来状态很好
Sheriff, cause you look great.
但是你就没有好奇
But aren't you at least a bit curious that.
你一天怎么能减下来这么多
You dropped ten a day.
告诉你们实话吧
Well to tell you the truth, agent.
我才不在乎呢
I don't give a flying fudge.
我丈夫Doug去年离开我
My husband Doug left me last year.
因为他说
Cause he said.
我喜欢曲奇奶昔胜过他
I loved cookie dough milkshake more than him.
我很抱歉
Sorry to hear that.
是的 Doug是个混蛋
Yeah, Doug's a dick.
你应该得到更好的人
You deserve better.
谢谢
Thanks.
但他说的没错
But, he was right.
那段是我的黑暗时期
That was a dark time for me.
谁说吃掉你的痛苦
Whoever said you eat your pain.
我才不是 我把痛苦一饮而尽
Not me, I guzzled it.
不管了
Anyhoo.
我猜我只想再次变美罢了
I guess I just wanted to feel pretty again.
而大峡谷健身中心帮我完成了心愿
And Canyon Valley did that.
唯一的问题是
Only question is.
你们在这做什么
What are you doing here.
我们在做卧底
We're undercover.
猜到这一点了
Yeah, sort of get that.
我们觉得这里和
We think there's a connection between.
市里的谋杀有关
Canyon Valley and murders in town.
有什么关联
What kind of connection.
吮吸痕迹
Suction marks.
你们说的是这个吗
You mean like this.
没错 那是怎么来的
Yeah, where's that come from.
这是我的治疗
My spa treatment.
拔罐
Cupping.
- 拔罐 - 没错
- Cupping - Yeah.
我还以为会很痛 可是
You know I thought it was gonna hurt.But honestly.
睡一觉就好了
A snoozed through the whole thing.
当我醒来时整整瘦了一圈
By the time I woke up, I was down two dress sizes.
拔罐前你有吃布丁吗
Before the cupping, did you eat any pudding.
答对了 把碗舔了个干干净净
Darn tootin.Lick the bowl clean.
你还记得是谁进行那次治疗的吗
Do you remember who did this treatment.
当然了
Oh, yeah, you betcha.
Evelyn你看起来好极了
Evelyn, you're looking great.
再减十磅 你就完成任务了
Just ten more pounds, til your goal weight.
你介意我占用我妻子一点时间吗
Do you mind if I borrow my wife for a second.
看起来真不错 女士们
Looking good, ladies.
新来的那两个不是私人健身教练
The new guys aren't personal trainers.
你在说什么
What do you talking about.
我做了一些调查
I did more digging.
我在他们的车里发现了这个
I found this in their glove compartment.
他们是联邦调查局的
They're Feds.
更糟糕 他们是猎人
Worse, they're hunters.
为什么猎人会在这儿
Why hunters' here.
或许是因为这个
Maybe because of this.
天啊
Oh, my god.
- 你是不是认为 - 是的
- Do you think - I do.
我们该怎么办
What are we going to do.
放心 我会处理的 你只要尽量销毁证据就好了
Relax, I'll take care of it, just get rid of the evidence.
虽然我不是健康主义者
Okay, I'm no health nut.
但是这么做
But that.
是不对的
Is just wrong.
好了 说吧
Alright, talk.
不是你想的那样
Ihis isn't what you think.
我没杀人
I'm not a killer.
那你是什么
Well, then, what are you.
我是吸脂怪
I'm a pishtaco.
鱼肉卷饼
A fish taco.
吸脂怪
A pishtaco.
就是秘鲁吸脂怪
It means Peruvian fat sucker.
没听说过
Never heard of it.
所以你们跟吸血鬼差不多是吗
So what, you're like the vamps.
只不过在饮食上更偏好脂肪
With a sweet tooth for cellulite.
吸血鬼杀人
Vampires kill.
我们只是寄生
We're just parasites.
好吧 这样
Well, in that case.
我是不会伤害人的
Look, I would never hurt anybody.
这就是为什么Larry和我开了这家大峡谷健身中心
Okay, this is why Larry and I started Canyon Valley.
我们帮人们减肥
We can help people lose weight.
而我也能够获取食物
And I could feed.
这是双赢
It was a win win.
是没错 但是你把两个人活活吸光了
Yes, except for the two you dysoned to death.
那不是我
That isn't me.
那是谁
Then who was it.
Alonso
Alonso.
餐厅里的那家伙
The dude in cafeteria.
他是我哥哥
He's my brother.
我知道你欲望很强烈
I know you're a lost cause.
你不像你妹妹那样强大有自制力
Unlike your sister, you are weak.
我也很高兴见到你 Larry
Good to see you, too, Larry.
你怎么能这样对她
How could you do this to her.
对我们
To us.
我怎么了
Do what.
这个
This.
哦 那个吗
Oh, that.
仅仅就这样吗
Yeah, that.
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what that means.
现在有猎人找上门来了
Now there're hunters here.
这都是你们的错 你个白鬼
It's your fault, blanco.
要不是你们俩不让我随意进食
If you didn't starve me maybe.
听着 你这个怪胎
Listen, you freak.
这个机构花费了我和你妹妹几年的心血
Your sister and I spent years building this operation.
如果你想要
And if you think that.
就这么毁了它
I'm gonna let you gluttony destroy it.
你是要付出代价的
You got other things coming.
我要你滚 马上
I want you out, now.
我不会离开Maritza的
I'm not leaving Maritza.
我这么跟你说吧 兄弟
Well I got news for you pal.
她也不希望你留在这儿
She doesn't want you here either.
要么你自己走人 要么我亲自帮你
Either you leave, or I'll make you.
我把Alonso从秘鲁带到这儿
I brought Alonso here from Peru.
就是为了向他展示一个更好的生存方式
To show him a better way.
一个更能被世人接受的方式
A more civilized way.
当我们不再是怪物的时候
One where we weren't monsters.
和人类和平相处的秘诀是
The secret to co-existing with humans was just.
进食适量让我们得以生存
Eating enough to getby.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
Alonso并不喜欢这种方式 对不对
Alonso wasn't a big fan of portion control, was he.
是的
No.
在进行常规治疗的时候
During the routine treatment.
他差点儿杀死了一个客人
He almost killed a client.
他吸食的脂肪太多了
He sucked out too much fat.
所以我就把他安排在了厨房后勤
I demoted him to kitchen duty.
避免与人类直接接触 吃罐装脂肪
No human contact, just fat from the jars.
但是他说
But he said.
我越是约束着他
The more I deprived him.
他就越饥饿
The hungrier he got.
现在有三个人死了
And now three people are dead.
我的丈夫
My husband.
现在Alonso在哪儿
Where's Alonso right now.
有个地下室
The-the basement.
他大部分时间都待在那里
That's where he spends most of his time now.
那她怎么办
What about her.
在她想明白到底是站在哪一边的之前
Well, until we have to figure out which side she's on.
都不能给她松绑
She's staying put.
我是站在你们这一边的
I am on your side.
既然如此 怎么才能杀死他
Okay, then how do we kill him.
嘿
Hey.
私人领地
Private.
你们一点机会都没有
You and stupido have no chance.
脂肪能让我们变得更强大
The fat makes us stronger.
你妹妹可没说这点
Your sister didn't mentioned that.
她出卖了你
When she ratted you out.
你骗人
You're lying.
我猜在你杀了她丈夫之后
I guess after you killed her husband.
她终于忍受不了你了
You're too monstrous even for her.
谢谢 非常感谢你们的帮助
Thanks for everything, we'd appreciate it.
嘿
Hey.
你们是怎么跟警察解释的
What did you tell the sheriff.
老一套
The usual.
又一个逍遥法外的疯子杀人
Psycho killer on the loose.
他们 通常都很吃这一套
They, uh, usually buy it.
我在一天里失去了所有的亲人
I lost my whole family today.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
能跟你谈个事儿吗
May I steal you a sec.
等这里都搞定了之后
When this place clears out.
咱们就准备让她们全家团圆吧
Let us make her a family affair.
等等 Dean
Wait, Dean.
我们不能杀了Maritza
We're not gonna kill Maritza.
她是个怪物
She's a monster.
是啊 但她救了我们的命
Yeah, who saved our asses.
是你说要把所有事儿
You said that you wanted to keep things.
都公事公办的
Straightly business.
如果我没记错的话
Well last time I checked.
我们该做的不就是猎杀怪物的差事吗
We were in the business of killing monsters.
我是想把所有关于我们俩的事情公事公办
I wanted to keep things straightly business between us.
但我好歹还有人性
But I still have a heart.
我被Gadreel附身的时候
What if I crossed path with a hunter.
万一被一个猎人发现了怎么办
Back when I was possessed by Gadreel.
我也有可能会死掉
I could have been up dead too.
但那是我的错吗 是我的选择吗
Well, I deserve that, I deserve to die.
那么买去秘鲁的单程票吗
So one-way ticket to Peru.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
嗯 嘿
Yeah…un hey.
怎么
Yeah.
关于你那天说的话
About what you said the other day.
我还以为你完全没听进去呢
I thought it didn't bother you.
你要知道 Sam
You know, Sam.
我救了你的命
I saved your head back there.
不论是在那所教堂里
I saved your head at that church.
还是在医院里
And the hospital.
也许我想得不够周到
I may not think things all the way through.
但是我做的所有事情
Okay but what I do.
都是最正确的选择
I do because it's the right thing.
我不后悔
I'd do it again.
这就是问题所在了
And that is a problem.
你认为你是我的救世主 是我的哥哥 我的英雄
You think you're my savior, my brother, the hero.
随时准备救我 即使在你搞砸的时候
You swoop in, even when you mess up.
你认定你的选择是值得的
You think what you're doing is worth it.
因为你不断的说服自己
Because you convince yourself.
你所造成的伤害并不足以压过好的结果
You're doing more good than bad.
但是你错了
But you're not.
Kevin死了 Crowley不知所踪
Look, Kevin's died, Crowley's in the wind.
我们还不知道怎么对付那帮天使
We're no close to this beating angel thing.
你来告诉我
Please tell me.
我活着究竟有什么好处
What is the upside of me being alive.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me.
你和我在一起
You and me.
我们一起并肩奋斗
Fight in the good fight together.
好吧
Okay.
就这一次
For just once.
别跟我撒谎
Be honest with me.
你不是为了我而救我
You didn't save me for me.
你是为了你自己
You did it for you.
你在说什么
What are you talking about.
我已经做好赴死的准备了
I was ready to die, I was ready.
我不应该活着
I should have died.
但是你
But you.
你不想自己一个人
You didn't want to be alone.
这就是全部的症结所在了
Man, that's what all this boils down to.
你无法忍受没有我的生活
You can't stand the thought of being alone.
我跟你明说了吧
I'll give you this much.
你有随时牺牲自己的决心 这毋庸置疑
You're certainly willing to do the sacrifice.
但前提是最后受伤的人不是你
As long as you're not the one being hurt.
你不是想开诚布公吗
Yeah, you wanna be honest.
我问你 如果当时我们俩情况对调
If the situation were reversed.
我是那个奄奄一息的人
And I was dying.
你也会为我做同样的事
You'd do the same thing.
不 Dean
No, Dean.
我不会的
I wouldn't.
在同样的情况下 我不会救你
Same circumstances, I wouldn't.
我要睡了
I'm gonna get to bed.